This season is sponsored by Korea Air Force
We're going to the far side to see what else is our Smita
My name is Wang Dachui
I'm an actor
I'm shooting a low-cost martial arts drama
This is too low-cost
What is children's toy testing?
It's already this quality
It's still a hair
Say you're not good at quality
You're not convinced
If you want to save the princess
Just...
Just from...
Just from my body
Can you please recite the lines first?
Come on
Use your best move
Jiuyang Shen Quan
It turns out that I'm using the fist method, Jiuyang Fist.
It sounds great.
I feel that a powerful power
is gathering in my fist.
My left fist is as hot as a flame.
My right fist is as cold as frost.
What's wrong with me?
I didn't even do any special effects.
It's too vulgar to just build it up.
It turns out to be Jiuyang Fist.
Ice Fire Nine Heavens.
Hey, how did you see this move?
This name is too personal.
It's too powerful.
As expected of the successor of Jiuyang Fist.
My life is completely ruined.
It's not ruined.
I haven't come up with a move yet.
I remember the day the sunset ran in the afternoon
That was my lost youth
Hey, can you stop thinking about these strange things
Since I have defeated the enemy
Then I should be able to rescue the princess
Yes
No, you have to defeat me
Didn't you just defeat you
Do you think that person was me
It's completely you
It's just a dress
Yes
Let's not admit it
This crew is too poor
Will an actor die
Come on
Let's make a decision
How should I deal with him?
The successor of the power
What happened to him?
I have no regret in my life
I did nothing
I remember that day
I ran in the sunset
That is my lost youth
Don't think about these messy things
I'm going to rescue the princess soon
Why don't you expect this at all?
Can this special effect be a little more?
I don't feel like it at all
And standing on the castle
It's the guy I've defeated twice in a row
It's not the same painting
The style is totally different
Young man, you finally came
The princess is locked in the castle
Under this
How many times have you memorized it
Still can't remember the lines
Just draw it from my body
Young man, I want to fight with you
It can't be that the king of the Middle Ages has become exquisite
Finally there is a decisive battle
My life is a misunderstanding
Misunderstanding your sister
Your sister fell off the cliff and fell to death
I remember that day when I was running under the sunset
That was my lost youth
My name is Wang Dachui
I never thought that
I still saved the princess
when I didn't want to save her at all
It's really this fire
You saved me
I'll give you a room tonight
I want a room
Why do you do this
Why
I don't want to work with such a poor crew anymore
Sorry, sorry
Sorry
I forgot to turn off the f**k
Hello everyone, I am Professor
Be sure to follow our official WeChat account, Wanxingren
Just say these three words, Wanxingren
Let's come together and learn how to make fun of
Let's play together